producing and interviewing the one and
only Joe
I believe we're on we're on g'day Joe I
think you know what the one and only
joke
there's three isn't it you're good
coming back and how many years
um before you start I brought this over
for Peter and I just sort of give it to
him he's coming from America give them
to a mate of mine and someone like that
and um sold as a giving between 51 to
to what they say 51 to 97 fuel economy
and um so this guy paid his money up
front and so on you've got to send your
money first you know this is um nearly
500 Australian which is
American what's it
well worth 75 cents anyway so he got one
cent and it was screwed together
all these top and screwed on and
everything's just like plastic and
everything else and so on and um it
won't work so it's not blue plastic you
know the old blue plastic bucket and um
anyway so sorry yeah right you can jack
as much as you like I'll try to stay
serious
[Music]
um
so you sent the first one in and it took
him a couple of months but finally got
it there and everything else in the um
he put it up to his vehicle and he's a
mechanic and Lismore does all the key
cutting got all the analyzing gear and
everything else so he put on his vehicle
and went for a random bar and buy him
back done all the testing and everything
else and found out didn't do a damn
thing so he thought okay I'm gonna pull
the piece and see what's in there now
this one here was threaded there so he
got her in in the undoneer and
everything else and when he pulled her
apart he found out that that on the end
of it on the end of those two fittings
down into here
he's um
two ordinary washes that ran just
ordinary
um you know my phone watching
like not even Stone well I don't know
probably probably wouldn't be stainless
if it was going to react because the
what could be I didn't didn't check
anyway so um another following who I've
been chasing him up or two and talking
to him he wanted for a diesel so I gave
him the same money and he said um you
know
um he typed the damn thing and it likes
everywhere and so on so the fellas in
America who sell the team called him
back and said how'd you go with that
cell and what do you reckon about it and
what can we get you to fill out paper
and everything else to say you know what
you like about Mary is a good stuff
biggest hunk of crap out she didn't do a
damn thing come on there's a small
answer
yeah so
um within three days later
this one arrives
free one it's all yours someone like
that so I just now getting the Peter but
he can pull it to piece and do whatever
he likes but no good as yourself but
these things here are out there all in
somebody's name to be sold
and so on but um and that's all it is is
just black
what's that Holy paper TV storage 100
Mil whatever yeah
and the only thing you get is a few
wires
that's expensive and the thing the best
thing about it what changes it from um
being anything else your brown seller
anything else is uh
well how did you not to do stuff is you
don't use caustic so to use drainage oh
good so it's funny yeah
what's in there but this is what's out
there and some of the stuff being sold
and it's useless
now we've got past a real serious stuff
we're on our group called Yahoo groups
Joe cell two site
there's been a um an acknowledgment
on some of the Suzuki video
um
inquiries
one of which is if you like you want me
to read it out cheers so everybody can
hear it hi Joe I hope you are well I
just wanted to thank you for all you
have done I truly believe you are the
one who made the greatest difference in
the world helping mankind
stop polluting our environment and
slowly killing ourselves with polluting
Energy Systems Peter thanks for helping
Joe get his stuff out into the public
domain I really do appreciate you but
to answer your question you posed in the
Suzuki video I just wanted to tell you
firsthand that I figured out what you
did in the Suzuki Suzuki video with the
Suzuki truck Joe you have reversed the
polarity of the entire system
does it require is that's not a question
I told you we were Dipper
yeah so he's had a question well is that
the end of it
Joe you say when you've done what what
you've done is reverse polarity type and
so on when you shut down the positive
side of the coil the alternator charges
the system in the opposite direction if
you demonstrated this while in the
restaurant with your fingers the
alternator is charging this way and your
battery is charging the other way later
in the video you mentioned a Suzuki
truck has a solenoid on the card and
this was put there to shut down the fuel
from entering the intake manifold the
solenoid Center is positive and the base
yeah the um
so here's all this about the Suzuki the
Suzuki is out there for all the years
now I'm I'm not a person doing anything
as you know and so on but so many people
come out there um sort of saying about
what Joe's done and what he's doing and
see myself here
um
this smart alec with the Suzuki
um was raving that he was a
well electronic squid yeah you can play
with all these and understand all these
things and everything else and so on but
um I feel like that tip that would be
pages
I mean little short ass but he's down
too far for me
so I just happened to be down
down at these fellas place not working
with him or do anything else and he was
mouthing off about this and that and
everything else all over the place so I
said yeah
if you know about cars and everything I
said I'll go and stuff yours I just went
out and no screwdrivers no spanners no
wait no anything and um
and just one little thing and then he
couldn't shut his vehicle
I said we'll figure that one out so with
all the people out there and everything
else professing there's so many sites on
the internet about what Joe sells are
and what they do and everything else you
know hydrogen producing machines
everything that's
it's a frequency
frequency that you're changing the game
vehicles vehicles are known to run like
pre-ignition and cold easily and
everything else and the timings out to
just change all that to suit and it
brings it back into order got a
condenser which is fully car don't go so
everything else is the same but
condenses out any of the electrics or
anything else on the vehicle shut them
down
okay so but what this vehicle does is
probably a few different things actually
the Suzuki
um technology that they're not knowing
so much is um DC generators government
took them a long time ago use them in
the um
Air Force they're in for sending radio
signals as far as I know around the
world everywhere and they don't tell you
about them but early early early
Vehicles had DC well you you wouldn't
call them a Magneto but that's what they
did called
DC Magneto and they only had one more
coming out of them there's no second
wire and that one wire just went and
screwed on the engine anywhere and that
was from a one cylinder up to a 12
cylinder motor and the engines run
right they just run there's no nothing
else required you don't need distributor
or anything else like that because see
you're doing away with it that frequency
or whatever else went into the engine
and fired the engine see what
was on fire the fuel air mix it's uh
vehicle
the thing was occurring and you girls
here said you you're um
your spark is jumping from the center
electrode over to ground and
um the spark isn't igniting anything
it's converting itself back into uh into
the block and back around through your
battery and I'll see you
talk right so um
few in your absence but that's all right
um
so where does that Spa come from
it comes back to the coil
okay and see you're positive and
negative going to your coil
um aren't actually producing this you're
not using any of them gotta
talk layman's terms I'm pretty lame
um
bringing it back to the where's his Spa
come from the coil which is called the
Tesla coil coil in the cars and
everything else is is um it's got a
primer and a secondary winding and
everything and what happens is you
you're um you're negative coming off
your block goes through your points your
condenser and then up into your coil and
goes around and comes out the other side
as positive your positive comes into the
coil
goes round round on the very early cars
and everything else she goes around
through your year-round primary
secondary nearing and it comes out as
ground negative so it's going in
positive it comes out negative now
you don't use any of them too
none of them are used up to actually
make the AC Spike or comes out the
center of the coil it is a um it's a 90
degree Spike
they're there and they create it but
it's not them that it's actually been
used up to make it
check that out it's a 90 degree Spike
so and on Commodore it's just giving for
you roughly quickly and everything else
Commodore has used something called
waste spark management forwards Ford
used it for a while wouldn't pay holder
and everything else so then as far as I
understand
don't hold me to that one but Ford had
on for a while and then took it off the
Commodore was used it on their v6s and
everything else where they
they use the positive side as well and
fire it now
just bring it up on the on the running
of the engine the negative is the thing
which has got the points or the braking
circuit in it for your compression side
of your cylinder and on the Commodores
they're far at Six Degrees before top
their Center so you know up here and
they fire and you're piston keeps going
and everything else and then it explodes
down the cylinder apparently
so all right so what
um
uh what the uh the Commodore motor is is
a 350 Chev motor right V8 but two
cylinders missing so they don't get real
good economy so the Holden and
everything else actually probably for
America or somewhere come up with waste
spark management
you break that down waist Spark
well they don't have waist spark they
have waste electricity
okay they're not using it so they
actually break it like on the negative
size broken by a set of points they
break the positive side now the positive
there's a complete opposite to the
negative
so the um the positive side is then
fired into
the opposite cylinder
of the the what the negative one is so
you have a um two cylinders coming up at
the same time
okay one is under compression
it's opposite when I look in that mirror
anyway yeah but anyway and um the sorry
because you're in Australia
that's it so the other one coming up is
on exhaust pushing the exhaust out
that's on the four stroke okay so you
have your exhaust valve open and they
fire that positive and break the
positive side and they fire that into
the exhaust cylinder it's six degrees it
fires at exact same time
okay that wasn't that wasn't exact but
close number so negative fires a
compression chamber so-called and the
positive is fired then into the exhaust
at Six Degrees before top which actually
creates the negative in the compression
chamber creates explosion breaks all
your gases apart and gives you you know
Heating and expansion everything else
well the other one actually
closes down and she pulls on the Piston
the head of the Piston maybe with the
valve open you've got to understand that
if you know about mechanics and
everything else Two Strokes shouldn't
work because the exhaust is open
um first then your intake and it's
compressing with the exhaust your color
fuel comes in your hot gas is going out
and it's compressing with a big open
hole it should run but it does anyway so
um what actually happens with the
Commodores in the Statue getting
implosion there's a positive creating
implosion in the exhaust burnt gases and
closes them down creates a pool gives a
smoother motor less miles per gallon
that you have to put in the first part
everything else so we take a motor which
is normally around about the who knows
if it's a really good carbureted one or
something injection one you might get 15
18 miles per gallon out of the original
V8 you know 350 Chev or something with
the V6
um you would get probably 20 something
but they're getting 38 to 40 miles per
gallon out of the v6s now because they
waste spark you can go to the computer
cut that wire and you break yourself
down to about 20 or so make your motor
run rougher noisier and you still gotta
go but you haven't got the go that
they've got so they actually created
this implosion to fire on that
on that side so they're using
the um you know the positive and the
negative and they call it way Spark
come up to date with all that and
everything else too you know check it
out but um
and that goes into two opposites illness
so it's double fires
okay so with your V6 is really a V12 but
firing on the compression and firing on
the exhaust and it makes a smooth motor
with good economy and everything else
okay so many people know about that as
such but anyway but your spa coming out
of your coil
is a 90 degree Spike you're not using
the positive or the negative for your
coil the you're using them there to set
up the field and when you collapse one
side of the field you get that going
across now dead if you look at the other
tapes I've put in here it's gotten
everything else on it that doesn't seem
to have a positive or negative charge to
it and what we understand if it had a
negative charge
then we know about magnetism and
everything girls electromagnetic field
collapsing and whatever else and the
magnetism is what positive similar repel
and the
black poles repel okay and Opposites
Attract so if there's spark I've asked
people if that spark was positive coming
out of your coil
then it would go to the negative
terminal at your battery in your circuit
but wouldn't go to the positive
but on the tape you find it going to the
positive and to the negative vice versa
if it was negative it shouldn't go to
the negative we go to the positive but
it's going to both
and then on top of it you've got a fuel
cell leg the battery is a fuel cell that
makes hydrogen oxygen they tell you
that um isn't not even part of the
question but it's a good understanding
so you can bring up to to start to
understand some of this they tell you
that hydrogen and all that can be fired
in the motorbike they Spark
your battery produces hydrogen oxygen
that's bad it doesn't blow the battery
it doesn't blow they get it actually
makes it if you look at the tapes that
pde now has and the only reason I give
that out there for anybody anyway is to
to see that there's different
frequencies that we don't know of
there's different things occurring that
we've been told and doesn't occur
right
and some things do occur when we're told
that they don't occur
okay so really back to it on the Suzuki
and everything girls yes
no spanners no screwdrivers no nothing
else but there is a polarity change
and not the way that you understand it
it's not it's not the same talked about
like down at the cafe
that was talking about generators
generators with polarizing them you know
reverse polarizing them with the
regulator and everything
this is an alternator
and
on the tape it's talking about the
alternator actually what that shows you
there the alternator squirrels head off
when we pull the wire off the the
positive for the coil not any other time
tomato rev it'll go good and everything
else while the keys on and while the
while the positive wires on the coil
okay but you pull a positive wire off
the coil
and you're automated hell just head off
and this follow says who's on these
um he says that um it's the
brand new belt that he put on there that
he
is
the one he had on there before done it
so he put a brand new one on there
put a brand new one on tighten it up you
still does it why because your
alternator is charging one way and being
driven one way okay and when we pull
that wire there and I haven't got to
tell you what's actually running the
vehicle in because not the old mate
and it's not the battery
um
it's something called a DC generated
non-regulated frequencies see a
regulator a generator has a regulator an
alternator has a regulator
okay we'll get to the next people it
doesn't in a second
the first DC magnetos or DC generator
fights with the one wire never had a
regulator
frequency that I've produced
keep in heaven
so when you're trying to comprehend that
as such try and figure out pre-ignition
and cold easily
the day pre-ignition these are only
talking about electric cars
okay you're not diesel vehicles we're
talking electric petrol driven Spike
Motors at the moment
okay there's a couple of Concepts there
what occurs where people don't
understand our Hydraulics won't go there
too much but our our hydraulics
they say scientists and everybody else
says that we have a liquid cannot be
compressed
okay well you put a little bit of water
into a diesel
miter and everything else and don't care
how fat the Conrad is or the size of the
Piston should you smash it to
Smithereens because she's 100 hydraulic
blocks okay one compressor but what
actually happens on the electric mode
okay you can grab the garden hose clean
shown to use and everything else
and Hitler had it and everything else
yeah you can tick to flipping water
stick water straight down the throat
pour it in turn the garden hose on and
turn it on full ball all you got to do
bring the accelerator up a little bit
yeah compensator doesn't cut out because
it's right that water goes in
it doesn't the amount that you can pour
in there doesn't actually evaporate
and then you can catch it in a bucket
Edge exhaust
okay it doesn't evaporate and then
condense again in the time that it's
doing it with the revs of the motor and
everything else you bring your ribs
right up it decodes the valves decodes
the Pistons unseasons sticky Rings
unseasoned sticky Valves and flaming
just freeze the motor but the Electric's
going through that engine takes away all
hydraulics
you can put in there with the motor
going
right and you don't get the hydraulic
block you turn the engine off put some
water down there or liquid or something
else like that and then try and hit the
cake Plumb you don't go anywhere
but if the engine's going and you put it
into there it's a different thing
happening all together
so now with the Suzuki we're not going
to offer we're still there with the
Suzuki and everything else
the key was turned off
pre-ignition coil diesel what is it
carry pre-ignition is we've been told
there's too much carbon on the Piston or
too much heat or someone like that in
the chamber
many things can cause pre-ignition too
much compression too much cabin
too much
you know whatever but the timing how do
you stop the pre-ignition so in
pre-ignition what you're doing is you're
starting your vehicle and then your
motor's supposed to be hot and you turn
the key off
so when you turn the key off
your motor don't stop
it actually starts to not run smooth it
runs different roughish okay so I can
make your motor run rough you can make a
motor run rough but just by grabbing the
distributor turn the damn thing out of
where it is now
okay you need to run Russell's guts
okay so the um
pre-ignition can be stopped in an engine
by just retarding the timing
and that's with the key on
okay just recharge your timing a
fraction
and so on and then turn the key off and
your motor just stops
so but if it's too far Advanced on the
timing
then she can run on
doesn't do it with every engine or
anything else you just you can make your
engines do it by just advancing
advancing too much the people out there
if you understand about pre-ignition or
if you had it happen find your keys
turned off now if your keys turned off
you've also shut down a few other things
one is if you've got a carburetor you
shut down the electronic you know the
solenoid
okay solenoid which is virtually double
wiring you know electromagnetic field
and that actually throws a piece of
metal either throws it out because of
the ways that you wounded and she pushes
across the hole and and shuts down the
engine
stops fuel going their protein isn't
Geminis and everything else actually
have it the other way winding and so on
it actually pulls up pulls away so it's
pulling into it so you've got to push
out and pull in that's the solenoid okay
so you shut down your positive you shut
down your solenoid you shut down the
fuel you're supposed to shut down the
engine
but people are turning their engines off
with solenoids and they're turning off
the coil
or are they turning off the coil and so
on which is your ignition spark positive
and the engines are still going
running rough as good okay so and that's
where the key turned off you've got to
start asking yourselves what is actually
happening when your engine is going by
either your generator or your
alternating everything else and you turn
the key off have you shut down the spot
shut down the forward Spark
and then your dash light comes on
okay because you're feeding the other
way and it's not the same spot
it's not the same thing all together not
even the same flaming stuff
anyway so
and the car goes so you haven't got your
solenoid you haven't got your coil
and you haven't got your ignition but
your car is still running
okay so why is it running what I've done
to pass near me when it's free ignite
and everything else I don't go and I can
I'm I can't I don't go always
I do for other people but turn the
distributor backwards the timing
and turn your key on and run it that way
okay because you out here your car rust
too
because we're running a negative Earth
so called here England runs a positive
Earth their bodies don't rush they don't
use butterfly chokes to shut down air
they use flooding jokes if they use
attractive or they sell into all their
cars hop in turn the key press a button
in all the wet weather
they're putting because of sleet and
snow and and everything over the
roads in England what they throw on the
roads salt
and when you put salt on the road down
here and drive your car around for a
while what are you gonna have
well in England they run that system
which is a positive Earth as such and
everything else and that stops the
rusting of the bodies and so on like
that okay and gives better start and
don't need to reduce in the winter time
they don't need to reduce the air to
give you more fuel so you don't splutter
and cough and backfire up through the
car but you never you can drive down the
road
they run positive Earth we're stupid out
here we run negative Earth and
everything else and so on and then our
bodies are us we get static electricity
in our vehicles and now where you need
in winter when a cold weather and we
need a butterfly choke to shut off the
air to give ourselves more fuel and
isn't that good really good
anyway so
and all these different things occur
because of them so
that's pre-ignition we can the
time what I do is on what I've done on
the vintage cars and some of the others
is I don't do that I turn the key off
and if it's very igniting I keep
advancing it
because what you're going to find here
is there's only a degree in where these
motors will fire
and if that's with the key turned on
within that degree there's top dead
center and you've got your circle and
the fires within that degrees on this
side
inspectors on there to take them here to
me on that side say six degrees before
top dead center because there's top dead
center Pistons coming up fires on left
side Okay so
if it's firing there and so when you
turn the key off where is your actual
spark or frequency going
somewhere else
let's put your timing out
so why won't your engine run with the
key turned off
it has got frequency sparkly it has but
it's completely reversed because the
engine's gone it's complete reverse and
it's put the timing over to another
place what I do is I Advance a
distributor
okay and what happens is you go
starts running smooth and then you can
accelerate with key turned off
with the engine going
you'll figure out how to start it
otherwise and what to do otherwise but
that's what I did and it actually runs
but if you want it to run properly with
a key on and you turn the key off and it
stops you have to re-card the
distributor so what now is the other
cold easily
okay coal dieseling is not a diesel
engine cold dieseling is an engine
which is actually you started when the
motor's cold and you turn a straight
back off again and the damn thing
pre-ignite or not pre-knitive
it's not pretty igniting because it's
hot it's now cold and it runs on
okay so is that okay
so
um
the cold easing is child engine turn the
key off she keeps going that's
Electric's almost shut down that's
ignition to the positive side of the
coil shut down and whatever else shut
down fuel pumps and everything else if
you want look at it the engine keeps
going but it runs rough
so how do you stop that
turned your key off
maybe shut down the spot what's making
the motor right
to stop your cold easily what do you do
you have to a fairly distribute it
because it's too far
gone out of that what's going out of
that
when you turn the key off
okay so you have to bring your
distributor up a little bit ahead
Advance it a bit and then you can start
your car and turn it off and she just
goes and stops it wasn't anything
running
when you turn the key off and everything
else you shut down why is it still a gun
when the timing is gone one way or the
other
okay now on the Suzuki we haven't gone
from
what we've got is a whole lot of things
here people haven't figured out what has
really taken place with the Suzuki now I
didn't say I was going to tell you every
single thing here just bring me up a
little bit onto something because see we
tell everybody everything and what do
you get they just call them they
still wouldn't know Joe yeah so
um
you don't you don't get any praise and
glory and I don't want it anyway and you
don't make yourself out to be anything
in fact you've got all everybody out
there who want to write about you call
yourself an idiot
right and then there's other people here
like this guy here I appreciate his
views and everything else but doesn't do
anything for me sorry about that but I
don't
care about praise and glory and I'm not
interested in what you think as such and
I'm not doing it I'm not doing it for
anybody or any reason or anything it's
just and I said to Peter you put it out
there and all it's about is that all
these things written about Joe and
everything else so he never put any of
them up there
and they're all being cross fusing all
these flipping information everywhere
and and getting it all out of whack
it's frequencies
it's not gases it's not petrols there's
not anything like that it's frequencies
what cars do I found out how you can
make cars run without that Peter Brock
same problem Pete now Dead showing like
that pity foreign but anyway Peter had a
car around without the fuels and people
thought he was on a fuel polarizer
you run out of fuel three laps earlier
fuel polarizers work with fuel
everybody
they just accepted what was told to them
but Peter has run an air polarizer
doesn't matter
I mean the Japanese name the car
companies know it happens to your
pre-ignition coal dieseling all these
effects that they run different metals
and engines they get all these things
happen and they don't want to tell you
and they don't want to give it to you
and they don't want you to know
and the science doesn't tell you about
any of this stuff as well and everything
else and we don't actually think about
what's taking place
the Suzuki again back to it
Suzuki with a key turned off on someone
like that doesn't pre-ignite and doesn't
call diesel
why well distributor hadn't been touched
the frequency in the distributor the
distributor is not turned
it's doing what it's supposed to do it's
not too far Advanced and it's not too
far it's where it's supposed to
be
okay
and I reverse polarity but not a normal
priority
and I didn't have a spanner or a
screwdriver or anything else to do it it
took one more
that's one that user going to have a
look at not me
because I'm not telling you the why
not yet
you just look at it and what it did is
that when the car is going what you're
seeing on the on the desk or tape or
whatever else
the alternator is fighting itself crazy
because the alternator is binding up the
fan belt
squealing crap is out of the female
because the alternator doesn't want to
go
in the direction
is going in the opposite direction
the alternator does not want to go in
the duration that that fan belt is gone
which is connected to the crankshaft and
that's why it's only howling when we
either turn the key off or pull that
water
at the
yeah coil
okay
all right breaking all down everything
else got to ask you is a few other
questions and you'll come up to what it
is what is a coil okay it's called the
Tesla coil it's got a primary and a
secondary and so on like that and uh
yeah you wind it what's in the middle of
those whinings
nothing
so I wanted to I wanted a Tesla fine he
found out if you don't do that and
everything else and you drive these two
fills to it and you collapse one side of
the fields nearing you get not a DC DC
you get an AC Spike
coming out now the DC might have a
positive or negative charge to it or the
positive may have a positive or negative
charge to it but that one out the center
at 90 degrees what has it got you just
check that out yourself okay if it had
ego either either one it would not go to
one or the other on the battery or the
fields in the engine if it's a magnetic
field that's what it says it is it's
collapsing electromagnetic field
okay
so and if it goes to both you figure out
why and how and what it is okay
and if you can't maybe some of the time
I'll tell you but
so you can use either side of the coil
and everything else so the coil doesn't
have a piece of metal in the middle what
is a song
or it does have a piece of metal in the
middle it's got the two mind engineering
the girls sets up electromagnetic field
if it's got a piece of metal in there
she'll either push out of its round one
you know went on one way or pull in if
it's around the other okay good now we
break ourselves down to a generator what
is a generator
generator is setting up the windings
and so on so it looks exactly the same
way that it's wound as the coil or
anything else but you got your two
you're positive and you're negative and
what's in the middle you've got a
circular piece of something in there
now if you turn it by the motor
you get electricity out of it
what happens if you drive electricity
into it
we haven't got generally you've got
yourself a stunt
okay because now putting electricity to
it actually turns
the generator
so your generator now into starter motor
so what's a starter motor starter
motor's got your two windings and
everything else in when you throw power
attitude turns the the shaft nearing now
if you um if you're an English type
starter motor you've got to Bendix
spring on the end until you'll actually
wind up and everything and throw back in
Via spring load but if you've got
yourself one of what we have on all our
normal cars and everything else we need
to apply two things on here now one is a
solenoid
so you've got two sets of
positive and negatives to do two
different things one is the starter
shaft turns doesn't throw out doesn't
pull in doesn't throw a spike
that look was another reason now the
um
so you spin it by throwing power at it
okay and the um and the starter modes
the same in England and Australia
either negative Earth or positive Earth
doesn't make any difference still turns
okay so you put a solenoid on and you
say starter turns and then your solenoid
pushes and throws that Rod out okay and
that engages into the flywheel and um
she actually starts to turn the flywheel
you may not have picked it up as such
and everything else on the tape
is what actually happens
to a starter motor
when the starter motor is being taken
past
the spinning ability on what you can
drive it with by the power what's in the
vehicle
in other words
the battery
the battery will spin the starter motor
at a certain speed
if it's six volt it spins at so many
revolutions if it's 12 volts see what my
thing and everything what happens if you
stick 12 volts on or six volts start
them out yeah
what happens if you stick six volts onto
a 12 volt start amount
okay you understand like a flat battery
so what happens if you take a starter
motor
and spin it faster than what the
original flame electricity pouring
through and around your circuits and
everything else actually does
while it's locked in
it's been driven by the solenoid lock at
the end of the
into the ring gear
and when you let the key go and
everything else a certain Revolution
does your ring gear throw it back out
not at high speed
she wants to keep throwing itself
forward and if you've got a reverse
polarity and everything else which isn't
that's that's not where I've done it
sorry it's not where I've done it but
what happens with the starter motor when
you overspin and past the point what
have they become
General
generating what
that other type of frequency which isn't
regulated
where does it go
well see it doesn't come otherwise
and it doesn't go down the watch okay
through the body of the
startup
and energizes the engine
it goes here through the shaft and ends
up as a DC generator and what do you see
around here can I call that either but
since I've got unregulated
DC feel what goes through into the
flywheel
up the Crenshaw
yeah it's a possibility there's a big
possibility that debt actually
can do the same as the DC Magneto in the
early days that they don't want you to
know about which is sending a film to
the engine what doesn't use that kind of
spark to actually it's not spark
frequency to fire the engines because
the spark that's nice fire the engine
you don't think so how do you check a
fully sparked by getting into it real
fast fully spark plug you know don't
care about anything we've got to miss 40
spark plug okay well without pulling it
out
okay I'm not saying one like some other
strange weird people
they can have a look at this now grab a
good brand new spark plug and drive the
end of the flame and tip down onto the
center electrode and think you've got a
fully spark plug no no that's a dead
short the only thing will happen there
is that your coil will jump spark
straight out of the center electrode
down onto the negative side because your
points are on their side
to jump straight down out of the center
onto the negative electrode
okay if it's negative there is a
negative side that you're breaking
because it's got nowhere to go it can't
go down there
but in a spike plug which is fully
carboned up or something like that I'll
crack them as a different happening down
there through the carbon or something
like that so she's not getting the right
frequency to fire your engine by the
spark how do you prove that it's a fully
spark plug
outside the engine
grab your spark plug lead
spark plug and there's your lead and you
go down that's missing take it away it's
missing
make the spark visibly jump in front of
you outside the engine what happens hmm
now they tell you that what you're doing
just building up charging everything
else going to jump in there it's dead
shorted in there through the carbon
there it's not going to spark you've got
your spice jumping out here
see what's happening at the end of
spotlight
you set up a different frequency
and you're not using the spark to
actually fire the petrol and Air
but you prove that you've got a fully
spark plug so you pull that spark plug
out and you throw it away and then you
stick the lead on and now the motor goes
hmm with this bike there but it was gone
without the spark there before the spike
was outside
you think about
okay so what is that frequency that
actually made the motor run without the
spark inside the cylinder or if it does
have a spark inside the ceiling if it
does then I'm wrong right if I'm wrong
on that then what's bites outside and
what's about it's inside
possibility that you could use our
frequency and throw away distributor and
spark plug leads and spark plugs and
everything else and run your engine on
that
Joe can we get rid of the motor
um Freddy Flintstones they tell me used
to got a hole on the floor and use his
feet but we didn't guide you you know
calluses could you use a different sort
of uh
um energy into the actual transmission
you mean just to drive the gearbox yeah
well they're doing that with electric
motors just with electric motors
and they're using electric and hybrid
cells and things like the juice spin the
salad in but if if that were the the
unit or can you use
it I don't know whatever
I'll let you get with it you know
the question I don't know
it comes in you know behind the electric
motors and so they only understand that
as such
um
gear ratio I don't know pedal cars pedal
things
whatever you want to do yes but
I think we're going to be backwards now
people want to go fast people don't want
to go back and reinvent the wheel
um
there are many many why is he doing and
everything else but anyway so let's
let's finish what it's actually
happening there is
one little tiny thing that took me about
three seconds
without a spat on a screwdrivers three
seconds underneath the bottom of the car
which does these things
and so far Naomi's been able to roughly
figure out or even come smoothly figure
out what's happened and it attached to
start with it is reversing the polarity
to some degree which isn't one that we
know of because it's fighting the
alternator and it's fighting everything
else when we bring the revs up on the
Suzuki you'll find out that your normal
spark which is in your spark plug leads
and there you go disappears so your
motor runs smooth up higher and you lose
the spark from your coil
distributor points condensed condenser
and everything else well we got this
back there yeah well when things are
missing off the coil then there is a
condenser which is going from the
positive side of the coil
it's not a condenser it is
but we call it a suppressor
okay suppressor if we want to look at a
suppressor and a condenser are saying
things primary and secondary as such and
what happens if we want a condenser for
our spark we hook it up on the negative
side of our coil with our points and she
goes through and makes a car run if it's
fully right you pull that out unscrew
the case off the body and then you can
pull your car at A Thousand Miles you
won't get a kick out of them with all
the spark everything else is spark there
one kick
okay what's a suppressor well the
suppressor is Earth ground outside case
the same as condenser
and the condenser goes to the negative
side
suppressor goes to the positive side of
the coil
and takes away the crackle out of your
wireless and everything else you know
what comes from your static out of your
alternator or any coil or out of your
your leads and everything else causes
this jumping vibrating pulsing feel that
really isn't even needed because
it's jumping across the center
electroding your spark plug back down
the ground to try and give you a flat
line
frequency
so you're
everything that we know of
doesn't run on AC
now okay you can put AC to it that
doesn't run on the AC your
um your TV
has to convert back to DC to turn it on
your video DCs are turned on your
wireless DC to turn it on your computer
DC to turn it on your jug has to go with
the coiling and everything else back to
DC you don't think it's DC AC will kill
you kick in knock your right over
one two three coils in The Jug element
they're in the water put your hand in
turn it on she'll just boil water she
won't kill you because it's converted
through a coil back to a DC you've got
all these things work for DC your engine
works Off DC frequency it doesn't work
or facing the spark plugs add to jump
the spark across the converter back to a
DC Flatline charge so it'll flame and
fire the engine
and um
and then some of the early early cars
never have they never had the points
never had the condensers never had the
refinement spark plugs never had
Distributors never had leads
and um
maggies and all that well I had the
adventure of Maggie and frequency spark
which I did do they did have you know a
breaking very big lacking flame and AC
kicked him
okay but then they had to use spark
plugs but go back before that they
didn't and back before that they didn't
okay you had all these different
Vehicles like
um you heard a petrol Cairo cars you
know
start them on petrol turn them over to
Cairo then they had Cairo not knowing
too much about it Caro water start them
on Cairo warming up and everything else
turn them over on the water and drive
all day on water
don't want you to have that Monita
okay
um
you know in the war when they didn't
have petrol so many ideas come out if
you want to chase them up so many so
many ideas come out look at um
uh charcoal burner
okay we've got one to drive around here
all the time charcoal then no fuel
well they don't got old tracker all
burned up carbon and everything else
reheat the DMC and the only thing you
can say is going in the engine it's not
a fuel it's not a gas it's not anything
else it's re burn or reheated up
charcoal
and for some reason it's putting out a
frequency that makes your motor run
already burnt away stuff
and all these follow signs never even
come up with an idea that have
reproduced a new gas or something else
like that
fine well if it did then you've already
exhausted all your burnt stuff
everything why can't they make you their
cash to run the engine is it hydrogen is
it oxygen is it for methane the alcohol
and what is it I don't know if you go
back and check it but it's just burnt
stuff that also um
so
there's a couple of things happening
with a Suzuki a couple of things first
of all
um
we are repolarizing and using a
different frequency to actually fire the
engine down low speed that's where the
key turned off and on and it's no
pre-ignition needed no coal dieseling
needed and it doesn't do the exit
because the district timing's right and
this frequency lines up into that to
work it out anyway
okay
and if you don't think there's anything
going through your coil over your girl
some song like that well should rethink
it
any really needing any electricians or
anything else here out there they say
you need an opposite
well they tell you need two wires or two
connections you're going to look at
Christmas tree lights they don't have to
you might plug it in one end here and
take it around the other end and plug it
in the opposite charge there but that
means that two things are running two
different ways up one more
okay one's positive one's negative if
it's a case or both are negative or both
are positive
positive plus a positive minus it's all
these different things you can play with
and figure out what's out there you know
hold
okay
not learned not they don't want you to
know as such people keep finding them
and everything else again
and they think they found something
wonderful and and maybe Tesla founded
maybe these other guys found that there
he goes and they just shut it all down
and don't teach anybody and then they
hide all the info and you have to
stumble across it again or somebody does
but these things are occurring naturally
in cars
and all I've done is I've played with
these things
very much play with them fan out about
them and use them
so the Suzuki user reverse player to
start with but then they're tapped into
something else when the ribs come up we
dropped out the frequencies the spark
the Everything by the coin nice bikes
for spark plugs so what was running the
engines
well-in smoothing point
except it was noisy
the engines got tapped yeah no and the
that felt on the alternator was Square
launcher
I understand that I already explained
that yeah the thing is that the um the
alternator is fighting would say you're
not running off the battery and you're
not running off the alternator what you
are running off when we get up in the
bridges we're transferring over and the
starter motor becomes degenerator by
being turned faster than it can can
normally be and it's our pudding and it
done now put back up through the wires
where a generator output which then has
to be regulated the damn thing goes out
through the center turning shaft
a way that they don't even think of
but see that's what a coil does car coil
goes out through the center of your
worried not in and out there goes out a
different direction 90 degree Spike same
thing happens on the starter Motors when
you wind them up too far they end up
with a new energy a new frequency and
new spark a new kind of call the spark
because there's no spark and it's not
being cut it's not being pulsed
this is a 100 flat Walling if you want
to feel it with your hands you're not
going to feel it
because you can't feel DC the only way
you can feel DC is if you're foaming
pulsive or turned off and once you go
think it's not flat
say
um
in in the car runs
and what I've done you work out any of
the other fellows out there just for the
present
you go out and um you figure out what I
touched and what I've done in three
seconds play because I can go back to
these followers okay you still can't
turn it off you still can't stop right
now
you're driving and not seven yet
yesterday I was down there again
everything else was still being driven
nuts because he's still stuffed on how
to do anything and he wants to sell that
vehicle too the way it is he told me
yesterday that he found something else
out
he found out another way to shut down
the engine that he didn't know how to
shut it down before he said it
this is how electronically mined it is
and then if he gets his state it doesn't
matter I'm not trying to run him down or
anything else it's just we all there and
me included are all under some
stories and we don't understand
every single thing we're not awesome
some things we haven't learned or know
about yet so I can't same say or calling
that he just doesn't understand solenoid
okay you didn't even know what the name
of it was on the carburetor to shut down
the fuel when you turn your key off and
to that wire you see I found another
wall that goes to that thing on the
carburetor you know that real thing with
he said yeah if I take that off with the
key and everything else I'm selling like
that and so and he said if I act that
out to the body he said the engine stops
I said that's a positive power going to
that wire and I said the the engine is
negative I said you act that out you got
a dead short through your whole system
I said wonder it didn't blow fuses and
everything he said well it did actually
at First and he said I had to bypass the
fuses
that's good so next time he does and it
sticks out lady's car is going to burn
but he found out to stop the engine
so
anyway
can we um
can we got another questions
well that's one question
and we've only got 10 to go Joe no
probably going well it'll cover a hell
of a lot of the questions I reckon it's
going to get fastening okay you're ready
there's something on the net at the
moment called the inventor runs an
engine on proton themselves never heard
of a proton okay do you know BJ no never
heard of bejo the guy yeah well I
thought it might have been John um
beam beams of gin
BJ JB you know have it with Colin lost
me so Jim Bain an alcoholic drink
maybe we've got the chili into it Jeff
it's good enough without playing getting
the alcohol there's a chap from
Bundaberg who says he knows you've been
doing a lot of work with you
know me how many people do I remember
I'm lucky to remember what day it is
okay good let alone how many people have
come past me how many people have rang
me up how many people have sent me stuff
off very very quickly the University of
New South Wales
uh did they run a 1976 Leyland V8 on the
bench for months with no radiator
nuts what they had I who the University
of New South Wales
no did um don't know all I do know
isn't it stop information
as far as I know and everything else the
original Rover and everything else was
taken from a professor who sort of now
is passed on to and so on we weren't
running down too much and so on but he
told
tell them
he went and showed this vehicle to the
RTA in Newcastle and everything else
hadn't done all these tests and so on
like that on it and then the RTA
Apparently one of the guys there fronted
out his place and wanted to get into
doing it with him and everything else
and then the vehicle sort of went
missing and the Victorian government as
far as we know ended up with the engine
out of the car
and
I've seen it once and I've heard about
other people seeing it and being there
and everything else she's the other car
with no batteries no exhaust no
radiators no nothing else and they can't
shut it down
there's no feel on board there's no they
can't stop it it's not even a sale on
board and they can't stop it they've got
cameras and everything else into the
cylinders taking shots of insulin they
still don't know what it's running on
that's the last thing I've heard about
that years ago the sun's flashing on the
thing all right okay we've got one
minute or two to go Joe okay so no have
you received numerous death threats
not lately no come on I'm not scared I'm
not in fear I'm not interested
um no no
now people have said out there that um
you know I've been threatened and I mean
you know hiding and all that that's crap
I stopped doing things because I chose
to stuff anybody else okay I got
threatened to send my kids back in the
post it's written in Nexus years ago and
everything else I chose not to have my
kids sent back in the post if I went
ahead and showed Beyond 2 000 and new
and um Nexus and everything else is um
all this technology so I just said no
sorry not coming because that's what's
going to happen to me kids
that's what I was threatening with I
don't need these threats I don't want
them I didn't do it for that reason so
stuff
stuff everybody I like it
come out right now we'll just wait till
they're taped around here no no it won't
run out too anyway good night no no no
thanks very much for um answering the
one question
as I said we've only got 10 10 questions
nine to go you're gonna change the tape
I want to copy this stuff the way it is
you don't cut that bit off there's
certain people out there aren't allowed
to do things yeah I don't don't
do the right thing they just don't give
me they don't come back there and do the
right thing you know they don't give me
what they steal they don't give me what
they find them you can't steal it and
give it back to you that's that's I mean
it's not stealing